{
    "subject": "resource/Hardcore_(2015_film)",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Sharlto_Copley",
    "human_readable": "The film 'Hardcore' stars Sharlto Copley.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9200787544250488,
            "question": "What is the name of the film starring Sharlto Copley?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9148095846176147,
            "question": "Name a film featuring Sharlto Copley."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.800210177898407,
            "question": "Who stars in the film 'Hardcore'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7739355564117432,
            "question": "Has Sharlto Copley won any awards for his role in 'Hardcore'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7714259028434753,
            "question": "Is Sharlto Copley an actor?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44445738196372986,
            "question": "What genre is the film 'Hardcore' likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4412020444869995,
            "question": "When was the film 'Hardcore' released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.38726359605789185,
            "question": "Where can I watch the film 'Hardcore'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.34640732407569885,
            "question": "Are there any other famous actors in 'Hardcore'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3356706500053406,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about the plot of 'Hardcore'?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The film 'Hardcore' stars Sharlto Copley.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1104_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other famous actors in 'Hardcore'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1104_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can I watch the film 'Hardcore'?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1104_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When was the film 'Hardcore' released?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1104_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1104_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1104_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1104_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1104_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1104_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1104_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1104_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1104_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1104_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1104_93.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because the documents provided contain information that confirms Sharlto Copley's involvement in the film \"Hardcore\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the movie \"Hardcore Henry,\" which features Sharlto Copley as a starring actor, thus supporting the given triple."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}